Rock & roll is where God and The Devil shake hands
American Satan is a thriller, drama, music film directed by Ash Avildsen.
A young rock band, half from England and half from the US, drop out of
college and move to the Sunset Strip to chase their dreams.
Johnny Faust, played by Andy Biersack.
Mr. Capricorn, played by Malcolm McDowell.
Kat Faust, played by Denise Richards.
Gabriel, played by Bill Duke.
Vic Lakota, played by Booboo Stewart.
Lily Mayflower, played by Jesse Sullivan.
American Satan is a 2017 American supernatural musical thriller film directed by
Ash Avildsen, who also wrote the screenplay with Matty Beckerman.
It was released in theaters on Friday October 13, 2017, and stars Andy Biersack, Ben Bruce,
Drake Bell, Denise Richards, Malcolm McDowell, Booboo Stewart, and Tori Black.
The film marked Larry King's final film role before his death in January 2021.
It won an award for Best Narrative Feature at the 2017
Oceanside International Film Festival.
The movie successfully launched the titular franchise.
The film explores themes of satan, murder, fame, drugs, devil.
The tone is emotional and intense.